export type QuestionsTypes = {
  id: number;
  question: string;
  answers: string[];
  correctAnswer: number;
  secondsPerQuestion: number;
  points: number;
};

export const levelsData: Record<string, QuestionsTypes[]> = {
  herald: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'On lane you need to farm?',
      answers: ['Creeps', 'Runes', 'Monsters', 'Crops'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 5,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'What hero have the highest attack range?',
      answers: ['Lina', 'Queen of Pain', 'Drow Ranger', 'Sniper'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'What rune will give you maximum movement speed?',
      answers: ['Arcane', 'Shield', 'Haste', 'Bounty'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 5,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'What is the main attribute of "Axe"?',
      answers: ['Agility', 'He is Universal', 'Strength', 'Intelligence'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 5,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Who owns the spell "Quill Spray"?',
      answers: ['Shadow Demon', 'Bristleback', 'Lone Druid', 'Death Prophet'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'The "Wind Lance" will give you?',
      answers: ['Attack Speed', 'Movement Speed', 'Armour', 'Agility'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 5,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Each lane is defended by?',
      answers: ['Towers', 'Robots', 'Creatures', 'Gods'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 5,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'What is the base cooldown of "Death Pulse"?',
      answers: ['4s', '6s', '2.5s', '5s'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'Who owns the spell "Rot"?',
      answers: ['Naga Siren', 'Pudge', 'Lone Druid`s Bear', 'Dark Willow'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Which hero will spawn roses on the ground to root you?',
      answers: [
        'Dark Willow',
        'Treant Protector',
        'Nature Prophet',
        'Enchantress',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 5,
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: 'What is the main attribute of "Drow Ranger"?',
      answers: ['He is Universal', 'Agility', 'Intelligence', 'Strength'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 5,
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: 'How many tiers does towers have?',
      answers: ['2', '1', '5', '4'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: 'What is the price of "Desolator"?',
      answers: ['3300', '3400', '3500', '3600'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: '"Gleipnir" is made out of?',
      answers: ['3 items', '2 items', '4 items', '0 items'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: '"Hand of Midas" will gave you?',
      answers: [
        '+40 Attack Speed',
        '+30 Attack Speed',
        '+45 Attack Speed',
        '+35 Attack Speed',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 10,
    },
  ],
  guardian: [
    {
      id: 16,
      question: 'At which level do you get your ultimate?',
      answers: ['6', '8', '7', '10'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: 'How many secret shops are on the map?',
      answers: ['4', '0', '2', '1'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 15,
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: 'Which one is 2875 gold?',
      answers: [
        'Helm of the Dominator',
        'Spirit Vessel',
        'Skull Basher',
        'Solar Crest',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 15,
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: 'Neutral tier 3 items appear at?',
      answers: ['25:00+', '30:00+', '28:00+', '27:00+'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 15,
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: 'Which rune will give you bonus XP?',
      answers: ['Water', 'Wisdom', 'Arcane', 'Bounty'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 21,
      question: 'How much armor "Blade Mail" provide?',
      answers: ['+7', '+5', '+8', '+6'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      question: 'What hero will have "Reincarnation"?',
      answers: ['Undying', 'Wraith King', 'Night Stalker', 'Phoenix'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 23,
      question: 'The "Stone Form" spell is owned by?',
      answers: ['Primal Beast', 'Earth Spirit', 'Elder Titan', 'Visage'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 15,
    },
    {
      id: 24,
      question: 'With how much strength does "Medusa" start?',
      answers: ['1.2+ 0.8', '18+ 2.2', '0+ 0.0', '22+ 0.9'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 25,
      question: 'How much does the "Cloak" item cost?',
      answers: ['825', '575', '750', '800'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 26,
      question: 'How many types of boots are in the game?',
      answers: ['7', '5', '6', '4'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 27,
      question:
        'How much agility was "Poor Man`s Shield" able to offer in patch 7.07?',
      answers: ['+5', '+6', '+8', '+4'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 15,
    },
    {
      id: 28,
      question: 'How much armor does "Shiva`s Guard" provide?',
      answers: ['10', '15', '16', '20'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 29,
      question: 'What will gave you 16% evasion?',
      answers: ['Elven Tunic', 'Talisman of Evasion', 'Radiance', 'Butterfly'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      id: 30,
      question: 'Water rune appear for the first time at minute?',
      answers: ['03:00', '01:00', '00:00', '02:00'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 15,
      points: 10,
    },
  ],
  crusader: [
    {
      id: 31,
      question: 'How much money does "Oblivion Staff" cost?',
      answers: ['1600', '1575', '1625', '1650'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 15,
    },
    {
      id: 32,
      question: '"Eco Sabre" passive is called?',
      answers: ['Vengeance', 'Echo Strike', 'Sixth Sense', 'Damage Return'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 15,
    },
    {
      id: 33,
      question: '"Legion Commander" can receive from Duel?',
      answers: [
        '10/20/30 Damage',
        '10/15/20 Damage',
        '18/28/38 Damage',
        '10/25/40 Damage',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
    {
      id: 34,
      question: '"Presence of the Dark Lord" does?',
      answers: [
        'Decrease Armor',
        'Decrease Magic Resistance',
        'Decrease Attack Speed',
        'Reduce Movement Speed',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
    {
      id: 35,
      question: 'What spell can provide immunitiy and movement speed?',
      answers: ['Divine Favor', 'Vampiric Spirit', 'Enrage', 'Rage'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
    {
      id: 36,
      question: '"Blink Strike" is owned by?',
      answers: ['Anti Mage', 'Riki', 'Queen of Pain', 'Void Spirit'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 15,
    },
    {
      id: 37,
      question: '"E.M.P" can take?',
      answers: ['Mana', 'Movement Speed', 'Damage', 'Attack Speed'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 15,
    },
    {
      id: 38,
      question: 'How much regen does "Roshan" have?',
      answers: ['15', '40', '30', '20'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
    {
      id: 39,
      question: 'In patch 7.22 "Vladmir`s Offering" provided X% damage?',
      answers: ['25%', '16%', '15%', '18%'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
    {
      id: 40,
      question: 'How much movement speed "Stormcrafter" provides?',
      answers: ['35', '30', '25', '0'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 15,
    },
    {
      id: 41,
      question: 'What is the most expensive item in the game?',
      answers: [
        'Helm of the Overlord',
        'Dagon',
        'Wind Waker',
        'Blink Upgrades',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 15,
    },
    {
      id: 42,
      question: 'How much hp gives you the "Force Staff"?',
      answers: ['200', '225', '150', '175'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 15,
    },
    {
      id: 43,
      question: '"Charge of darkness" base cooldown is?',
      answers: ['11s', '12s', '13s', '14s'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 20,
      points: 15,
    },
    {
      id: 44,
      question: 'What is the duration of "Warcry"?',
      answers: ['6s', '8s', '10s', '12s'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
    {
      id: 45,
      question: 'What is the critical damage of "Mortal Strike"?',
      answers: ['400%', '350%', '300%', '250%'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
  ],
  archon: [
    {
      id: 46,
      question: 'What hero can share armor and transfer heal to the owner?',
      answers: ['Lone Druid', 'Wraith King', 'Sven', 'Centaur Warrunner'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 47,
      question: '"Dead in the Water" shard is owned by?',
      answers: ['Naga Siren', 'Tidehunter', 'Slark', 'Kunkka'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
    {
      id: 48,
      question: 'At level 20 "Kunkka" can choose?',
      answers: [
        '+45 Damage',
        'Ghostship Fleet',
        '-4s Torrent Cooldown',
        '+65% Tidebringer Cleave',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
    {
      id: 49,
      question: 'What is the base damage of "Timber Chain"?',
      answers: ['55', '60', '65', '50'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 50,
      question: '"Hand of God" is owned by?',
      answers: ['Zeus', 'Omniknight', 'Chen', 'Keeper of the Light'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
    {
      id: 51,
      question: 'What is the mana cost of "Guardian Angel"?',
      answers: ['75/125/150', '125/175/225', '150/200/250', '100/150/200'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 52,
      question: 'What is the cooldown of "Rolling Boulder"?',
      answers: ['4s', '8s', '6s', '3s'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 53,
      question: 'In what patch "Ring of Aquila" was removed from shop?',
      answers: ['7.23b', '7.19b', '7.23', '7.20'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 54,
      question: 'What is the duration of "Pit of Malice"?',
      answers: ['10s', '11s', '12s', '13s'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
    {
      id: 55,
      question: 'The "Psi Blades" damage type is?',
      answers: ['Physical', 'True Strike', 'Pure', 'Magical'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
    {
      id: 56,
      question: 'At level 15 "Tusk" can choose?',
      answers: [
        '+325 Health',
        '+125 Snowball Damage',
        '+25 Tag Team Damage',
        '-5s Ice Shards Cooldown',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 57,
      question: 'How much damage "Eidolon`s" can do?',
      answers: ['21/30/39/48', '20/28/38/47', '19/29/39/49', '20/27/37/48'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 58,
      question: 'At level 15 "Shadow Demon" can choose?',
      answers: [
        '-3s Disruption',
        '+12 Strength',
        '+25 Movement Speed',
        '+75 Cast Range',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
    {
      id: 59,
      question: 'Which strength stat is owned by "Phoenix"?',
      answers: ['22 + 3.5', '21 + 3.2', '23 + 3.3', '24 + 3.1'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
    {
      id: 60,
      question: '"Skull Basher" damage is?',
      answers: ['+24', '+26', '+28', '+30'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 20,
    },
  ],
  legend: [
    {
      id: 61,
      question: 'How much armor "Vladmir`s Offering" provides?',
      answers: [
        '+2 + 2 for Nearby Allies',
        '+3 + 2 for Nearby Allies',
        '0 + 4 for Nearby Allies',
        '+3 + 0 for Nearby Allies',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 62,
      question: 'What is the price for "Heaven`s Halberd"?',
      answers: ['3350', '3400', '3450', '3500'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 63,
      question:
        'How much damage does "Witch Blade" deals from your intelligence?',
      answers: ['0.65x', '0.70x', '0.75x', '0.80x'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 64,
      question: 'How much HP does a Melee Creep have?',
      answers: ['450', '500', '550', '600'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 65,
      question: 'In which patch the "Necronomicon" was removed?',
      answers: ['7.30', '7.29', '7.27', '7.28'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 66,
      question: 'How much hp does Ancient have?',
      answers: ['4250', '4500', '4750', '5000'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 67,
      question: 'Who owns the shard named "Shield of the Scion"?',
      answers: ['Visage', 'Skywrath Mage', 'Void Spirit', 'Arc Warden'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 68,
      question: 'What is the base attack speed of "Alchemist"?',
      answers: ['120', '121', '122', '124'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 69,
      question:
        'What is the bonus attack range generated by "Lightning Hands"?',
      answers: ['50', '75', '125', '100'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 70,
      question: 'What is the correct scalling of "Ion Shell"?',
      answers: ['21/24/27/30', '20/22/24/28', '21/23/25/29', '20/23/26/29'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 71,
      question: 'In which patch "Pudge" was introduced?',
      answers: ['5.35', '5.10', '4.33', '5.31'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 72,
      question: 'What hero owns the spell "Static Remnant"?',
      answers: ['Disruptor', 'Ember Spirit', 'Storm Spirit', 'Earth Spirit'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 73,
      question: 'Which creep will break your passive spells?',
      answers: [
        'Hill Troll Berserker',
        'Kobold Foreman',
        'Ghost',
        'Ogre Frostmage',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 74,
      question: 'Which agility stat is owned by "Pangolier"?',
      answers: ['18 + 2.1', '16 + 3.2', '18 + 2.5', '17 + 2+9'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
    {
      id: 75,
      question: '"Beastmaster" boar base health is?',
      answers: [
        '250/400/550/700',
        '300/450/600/750',
        '275/425/575/725',
        '325/475/625/775',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 25,
      points: 25,
    },
  ],
  ancient: [
    {
      id: 76,
      question: 'What was the price for "Wraith Pact"?',
      answers: ['4000', '3700', '3800', '3900'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 77,
      question: 'What is the base hp and mana of "Pugna"?',
      answers: ['531/392', '538/387', '526/406', '544/381'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 78,
      question: '"Berserker`s Rage" is owned by?',
      answers: ['Primal Beast', 'Alchemist', 'Huskar', 'Troll Warlord'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 79,
      question: 'At level 25 "Venomancer" can choose?',
      answers: [
        'Noxious Plague Aura reduces 200 AS',
        '+1.75% Noxious Plague Max HP Damage',
        '25% Poison Sting HP Regen Reduction',
        '2.25x Plague Ward HP/Damage',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 80,
      question: 'What is the chance for "Storm Surge" to land a strike?',
      answers: ['15%', '16%', '20%', '18%'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 81,
      question:
        'The "Aghanim`s Scepter" upgrade for "Necromastery" will increase max souls at?',
      answers: ['26', '24', '25', '28'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 82,
      question: 'How many stats can "Timbersaw" take with his first spell?',
      answers: ['13%', '15%', '14%', '12%'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 83,
      question: 'How much damage will "Intimidate" take from you?',
      answers: ['35%', '50%', '25%', '60%'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 84,
      question: 'The "War Stomp" damage is?',
      answers: ['25/50/75/150', '25/50/75/100', '50/100/150', '75/150/225'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 85,
      question: 'What is the cooldown of "Last Word" spell?',
      answers: ['110', '110/95/80', '25/20/15/10', '22/18/14/10'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 86,
      question: 'Which spell will deal damage based on the distance?',
      answers: ['Shadowraze', 'Impetus', 'Assassinate', 'Sacred Arrow'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 87,
      question: 'What is the base armor of "Batrider"?',
      answers: ['3.8', '4.5', '5.4', '4.8'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 88,
      question: 'What is the cooldown of "Sinister Gaze"?',
      answers: ['24/22/20/18', '26/24/22/20', '22/20/18/16', '28/26/24/22'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 89,
      question: 'How much spell amplification does "Meteor Hammer" provide?',
      answers: ['0', '5%', '10%', '24%'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 90,
      question:
        '"Three orbs of remarkable power bound within a single scepter"?',
      answers: ['Eye of Skadi', 'Soul Booster', 'Apex', 'Giant`s Ring'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
  ],
  divine: [
    {
      id: 91,
      question: 'Who has the less armor between this heroes?',
      answers: ['Riki', 'Razor', 'Enchantress', 'Kunkka'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 92,
      question: 'From the following list, which item will give +10 strength?',
      answers: [
        'Vambrace',
        'Ogre Seal Totem',
        'Drum of Endurance',
        'Ultimate Orb',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 93,
      question: 'What is the gold bounty of "Ancient Black Drake"?',
      answers: ['35-41', '37-43', '41-47', '39-45'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 94,
      question: 'How much gold does Tier 4 Tower drop per player?',
      answers: ['135', '155', '145', '165'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 95,
      question: 'Watchers will provide each team with X vision?',
      answers: ['900', '600', '700', '800'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 96,
      question: 'At level 10 "Grimstroke" can choose?',
      answers: [
        '-5s Ink Swell Cooldown',
        '+12% Ink Swell MS',
        '+65 Phantom`s Embrace DPS',
        '+25% Soulbind Spell DMG',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 97,
      question: 'What is the base burn damage duration of "Infernal Blade"?',
      answers: ['4s', '3.5s', '4.5s', '3s'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 98,
      question: '"Treant Protector" base armor is?',
      answers: ['2.2', '1.5', '2.5', '1.8'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 99,
      question: 'What is the maximum chance of "Coup de Grace" attack?',
      answers: ['25%', '24%', '22%', '18%'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 100,
      question: 'What is the base attack speed of "Chaos Knight"?',
      answers: ['122', '116', '119', '118'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 101,
      question: 'This base values of HP and Mana "626/255" are owned by?',
      answers: ['Brewmaster', 'Doom', 'Tiny', 'Beastmaster'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 102,
      question: 'Which strength scaling belongs to "Night Stalker"?',
      answers: ['23 + 4.1', '26 + 2.8', '24 + 3.7', '25 + 3.0'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 103,
      question: 'Which one is 5200 gold?',
      answers: [
        'Harpoon',
        'Shiva`s Guard',
        'Heart of Tarasque',
        'Eye of Skadi',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 30,
      points: 30,
    },
    {
      id: 104,
      question: '"Glassify" passive is owned by?',
      answers: [
        'Mirror Shield',
        'Seer Stone',
        'Nemesis Curse',
        'Eye of the Vizier',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 105,
      question: 'What is the range of "Buckler"?',
      answers: ['1000', '1100', '1200', '800'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
  ],
  immortal: [
    {
      id: 106,
      question: 'At which level the respawn time starts from 46s?',
      answers: ['15', '13', '17', '11'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 107,
      question: 'How much damage a Tier 2 Tower does have?',
      answers: ['144-148', '170-174', '156-160', '182-186'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 108,
      question: 'What is the movement speed of "Siege Creep"?',
      answers: ['315', '320', '325', '330'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 109,
      question:
        'Which item will give you +500 HP? (The conversion from strength also work)',
      answers: ['Magic Lamp', 'Havoc Hammer', 'Mirror Shield', 'Giant`s Ring'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 110,
      question: 'What is the "Linken`s Sphere" cooldown?',
      answers: ['13s', '16s', '14s', '15s'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 111,
      question:
        'What is the channel time of a tp scroll with "Boots of Travel" level 2 upgrade?',
      answers: ['2.5s', 'Isn`t applied', 'Same as level 1', '2s'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 112,
      question: 'What is the maximum duration of "False Promise"?',
      answers: ['10s', '11.5s', '12s', '7.5s'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 113,
      question: 'What hero will get +30 MS talent at level 20?',
      answers: ['Outworld Destroyer', 'Bane', 'Marci', 'Lina'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 114,
      question: '"Mud Golem" will drop?',
      answers: [
        '18-22 Gold Bounty',
        '20-24 Gold Bounty',
        '22-26 Gold Bounty',
        '24-28 Gold Bounty',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 115,
      question: '"Melee Barracks" will have a helth regen per second of?',
      answers: ['5.0', '0.0', '4.5', '10.0'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 116,
      question: 'How much health "Ancient Thunderhide" does have?',
      answers: ['2100', '2300', '1700', '1900'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 117,
      question: 'How much damage a Tier 4 Tower does have?',
      answers: ['192-196', '184-188', '198-202', '170-174'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 118,
      question: 'How many minutes does a "Sentry Ward" last?',
      answers: ['8', '6', '5', '7'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 119,
      question: 'How much "Magic Resistance" does "Roshan" have?',
      answers: ['45%', '55%', '60%', '50%'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
    {
      id: 120,
      question: 'How much health is restored after consuming the "Cheese"?',
      answers: ['2000', '1500', '2500', '1750'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 35,
      points: 35,
    },
  ],
  leaderboard: [
    {
      id: 121,
      question: 'What is the mana cost of "Refresher Shard"?',
      answers: ['0', '200', '150', '250'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 122,
      question: 'What is the base attack damage of "Silencer"?',
      answers: ['46-60', '43-57', '50-64', '40-54'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 123,
      question: 'Who has more mana?',
      answers: ['Anti-Mage', 'Lone Druid', 'Drow Ranger', 'Juggernaut'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 124,
      question: 'How much health bonus "Roshan`s Banner" provide?',
      answers: ['75%', '50%', '45%', '85%'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 125,
      question: 'How much damage "The Shining" passive will deal per second?',
      answers: ['0', '15', '45', '30'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 126,
      question: 'How much XP does level 25 requires?',
      answers: ['4000', '3000', '2500', '3500'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 127,
      question: 'What is the MS of "Feel Spirit"?',
      answers: ['350', '380', '270', '320'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 128,
      question: 'Which item will give you +7 Strength & +7 Intelligence?',
      answers: ['Holy Locket', 'Diadem', 'Drums of Endurance', 'Vambrace'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 129,
      question: 'What is the range of "Rod of Atos"?',
      answers: ['800', '1100', '900', '1200'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 130,
      question: 'What is the duration of "Shine"?',
      answers: ['8s', '6s', '7s', '9s'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 131,
      question: '"Insight Aura" will provide?',
      answers: [
        'Mana Regen & Health Regen',
        'Magic Barrier',
        'Magic Resistance & Health Regen',
        'Armor & Lifesteal',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 132,
      question: 'The damage of "Chain Lightning" is?',
      answers: ['135', '95', '150', '120'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 133,
      question:
        'How much HP regen the "Light Collector" will provide during the day?',
      answers: ['0', '15p/s', '10p/s', '12p/s'],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 134,
      question: 'How much strength will gain "Visage" per level?',
      answers: ['+1.1', '+2.4', '+3.0', '+1.8'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
    {
      id: 135,
      question: '"Cold Blooded" spell is owned by?',
      answers: ['Medusa', 'Ancient Apparition', 'Winter Wyvern', 'Huskar'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      secondsPerQuestion: 40,
      points: 40,
    },
  ],
};
